

+92.307.6475006



numanbhatti599@gmail.com



Other, Gujranwala, Pakistan

Summary

I am an experienced IT Security Specialist with a passion for upholding the highest standards of information security. I have over 1 + years of experience in monitoring and maintaining IT security systems, implementing security policies and managing security- related projects. I am highly organized and have worked with organizations of all sizes to ensure a secure and efficient information security system. I am also skilled at developing security plans, training personnel in security protocols, troubleshooting issues and responding to security threats.

Skills

Security System Troubleshooting | Security Risk Assessment | Penetration Testing | Network Security | Multi-tasking | IT Security Policies & Procedures | ISO27001 Compliance | incident response | Data Encryption/Decryption

Experience

Jul 2023 - Present

Junior It Security Officer

Brackets Pvt Ltd, Gujranwala, Pakistan

- 1. Developed and implemented security policies, procedures, and standards in accordance with the organizations security requirements
- 2. Monitored security systems and conducted regular audits to ensure compliance with the established security policies and protocols
- 3. Assisted with incident response plans and procedures in the event of security violations
- 4. Provided technical support and advice on security systems, including troubleshooting network and system-level security issues
- 5. Conducted security penetration testing and vulnerability assessment programs to identify weak spots in the organizations security system
- 6. Conducted security risk assessment to identify potential security threats and ensured security compliance

Oct 2021 - Jun 2022

Junior It officer

TCS (Private) Limited, Gujranwala, Pakistan

Hardware and Software Installation.

Implement Security Measures.

Technical User Support.

Diagnosing Software and Hardware Issues.

Manage information technology and Computer Systems.

Responding to Breakdown.

Aug 2019 - Dec 2020

Teaching

Royal Academy Of Computer Education, Gujranwala, Pakistan

Powered by **rozee**.Dk Planning lessons and activities that facilitate students\' acquisition of basic and advanced computer skills.Instructing in a manner that develops students\' confidence in their abilities.Observing and managing classroom dynamics.

Education

2023 National College of Business Administration & Economics (NCBA&E)

Bachelors in Science, BSCS

Computer Science

CGPA: 3.1/4

2018 Punjab College Gujranwala

Intermediate/A-Level, Fsc Pre Engineering

mathematics, chemistry, physics

Grade: B

2016 The Pakistan school Gujranwala

Matriculation/O-Level , matric

Biology, Mathematics, Chemistry

Grade: A

Languages

EnglishUrduExpertExpert